Guide to the Office of Residential Life records, 1946-2012 and undated UA.09.06.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Symposium - Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life: A Community by Women, 1963 Mar (Box 28)
- Telephone Expenses, 1971-1972 (Box 28)
- The University Experience - Duke YM/YMCA, 1969-1977 (Box 28)
- Town House Apartments, 1966-1968 (Box 28)
- Transfer Students, 1974-1976 (Box 28)
- Treasurer's Codes & Information - Woman's College, 1961-1973 (Box 28)
- Trinity College Staff - Meetings & Memoranda, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
- Trips (Living/Learning), 1978-1986 and undated (Box 28)
- Twentieth Century America Program (Baldwin Federation), 1974 (Box 28)
- Undergraduate Judicial Board - Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 28)
- Undergraduate Students Living Off Campus, 1973-1974 (Box 28)
- University Union, 1971-1972 (Box 28)
- University Union Board, circa 1973-1976 (Folder 1) (Box 28)
- University Union Board, circa 1973-1976 (Folder 2) (Box 28)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Correspondence, 1989 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Correspondence, 1990 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Correspondence, 1991 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Correspondence, 1992 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Correspondence, 1993 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Invoices, 1989 (Box 29)
- (Duke's) Vision Program Invoices, 1990 (Box 29)
- Vision (Duke's) Program Invoices, 1991 (Box 30)
- Vision (Duke's) Program Invoices, 1992 (Box 30)
- Vision (Duke's) Speakers (Angelou and Prospects), 1989-1992 (Box 30)
- Visitation Policy - Proposed Change, 1971-1972 (Box 30)
- Wannamaker IV & Guild Proposal, 1973 (Box 30)
- West Edens Link Residential Hall - Design Background, 2000 (Box 30)
- Who's Who Among Students, 1969-1973 (Box 30)
- Wilson House/Faculty Apartments/Pent House, 1959-1974 (Box 30)
- Wilson House & Guest Suite, 1973 (Box 30)
- Windsor House, 1974-1975 (Box 30)
- Woman's College - House & WSGA Budget, 1965-1971 (Box 30)
- Woman's College Judicial Board - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 30)
- Woman's College Judicial Board - Regulations, 1967-1972 (Box 30)
- Woman's College Judicial Board - Regulations/Handbooks, 1965-1967 (Box 31)
- Woman's College Judicial Structure (include Watson Report), 1968-1971 (Box 31)
- Women's Recreation Association - Budget, 1963-1972 (Box 31)
- Women's Recreation Association Manual, 1960-1964 (Box 31)
- Workbook File, 1973 (Box 31)
- Work Plan - Office of the Dean of Men, 1964 (Box 31)
- Work Reports - Office of the Dean of Men, undated (Box 31)
- Work-Study Program, 1974-1975 (Box 31)
- YM-YMCA, 1973 (Box 31)
- York House, 1972-1975 (Box 31)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1957-1958 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1958-1959 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1960-1961 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1962-1963 (Box 32)
- Activities - Summary Studies, 1963-1965 (Box 32)
- Alpha Tau Omega - Activities Studies Sample, 1957-1964 (Box 32)
- East Campus - Proposed Campus Plan and Implementation Strategy, 1987 (Box 32)
- Fraternity Materials for Staff Meetings, 1957-1960 (Box 32)
- Survey Results - Off Campus, 1972 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Women's Cross Sectional, 1972 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Fraternities, 1972 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Co-ed Dorms, 1972 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Co-ed Comparisons, 1973 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Freshman Comparisons, 1973 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Year Comparison, 1973 (Box 33)
- Survey Results - Federation Comparison - 2nd Year, 1973 (Box 33)
- Residential Feasibility Report, 1999 (Box 34)
- A Proposal to Fund Capital Priorities, 1999 (Box 34)
- Duke Upperclass Residential Programming, 1999 (Box 34)
- Appendix to Residential Program Feasibility Report, 1999 (Box 34)
- Duke University Campus Planning Studies - Draft, 1987 (Box 35)
- SFAC Meeting Minutes (7 Audio Tapes), 1968-1969 (Box 35)
- Hearing Committee - Pickets and Protests (2 Audio Tapes), undated (Box 35)
- Sound Off Night (3 Audio Tapes), undated (Box 35)
- [No Title] (1 Audio Tape), undated (Box 35)
- Dean-on-call and RC-on-call Protocol Manual, 2011-2012 (Box 36)
- Fall Training slides, circa 1990s (Box 36)
- Training slideshow, circa 1986 (Box 36)
- Duke University New Student Orientation Video, 1990 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09060002-VHS-0001)
- Duke University Honor Code Orientation, 1998 (Box 36, Video-cassette UA09060002-VHS-0002)
- Residential Advisors staff scrapbook, 1976-1977 (Box 37)
- Residential Advisors staff scrapbook, 1979-1980 (Box 37)
- Residential Advisors staff scrapbook, 1983-1984 (Box 38)
- Residential Advisors staff scrapbook, 1984-1987 (Box 39)
- Residential Advisors staff scrapbook, 1987-1988 (Box 39)